export const QuestionOne = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "My grandfather was ___ to the hospital yesterday?",
    answers: [
      { id: 1, content: "prescribed" },
      { id: 2, content: "admitted" },
      { id: 3, content: "accepted" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "admitted",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "There were two doctors ___ (=working) when we arrived.",
    answers: [
      { id: 1, content: "doing their duty" },
      { id: 2, content: "on demand" },
      { id: 3, content: "on duty" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "on duty",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "P1 : Does the patient have health___? P2 : No , she is uninsured.",
    answers: [
      { id: 1, content: "assurance" },
      { id: 2, content: "insurance" },
      { id: 3, content: "assistance" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "insurance",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "If you're unable to quit smoking altogether , you should at least ___(=do it less)",
    answers: [
      { id: 1, content: "cut down" },
      { id: 2, content: "cut off" },
      { id: 3, content: "cut around" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "cut down",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Everything went smoothly.There were no ___.",
    answers: [
      { id: 1, content: "complications" },
      { id: 2, content: "compliments" },
      { id: 3, content: "completions" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "complications",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: `To "OD (oh-dee) means to ___ (on a drug , etc)`,
    answers: [
      { id: 1, content: "overdrive" },
      { id: 2, content: "overkill" },
      { id: 3, content: "overdose" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "overdose",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "I've been taking birth control pills ___ (=for many years)",
    answers: [
      { id: 1, content: "for years" },
      { id: 2, content: "on a yearly basis" },
      { id: 3, content: "yearly" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "for years",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      "There's nothing to worry about.This is a ___(=standard) procedure.",
    answers: [
      { id: 1, content: "routine" },
      { id: 2, content: "routing" },
      { id: 3, content: "rooted" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "routine",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "Even if you are infected , the symptoms might not ___(=appear) for weeks.",
    answers: [
      { id: 1, content: "show off" },
      { id: 2, content: "show up" },
      { id: 3, content: "show" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "show up",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "This is a contagious disease that can only be ___ by/through sexual intercourse.",
    answers: [
      { id: 1, content: "transferred" },
      { id: 2, content: "transplanted" },
      { id: 3, content: "transmitted" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "transmitted",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question:
      "If pain disappears and then comes back again , it's referred to as '___'pain.",
    answers: [
      { id: 1, content: "recurrent" },
      { id: 2, content: "reclusive" },
      { id: 3, content: "current" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "recurrent",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "We'll have to ___(=do) some blood tests.",
    answers: [
      { id: 1, content: "race" },
      { id: 2, content: "run" },
      { id: 3, content: "jog" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "run",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "I need you to___.",
    answers: [
      { id: 1, content: "take a heavy breath" },
      { id: 2, content: "make a deep breath" },
      { id: 3, content: "take a deep breath" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "take a deep breath",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "I___the patient last week.He seemed very healthy.",
    answers: [
      { id: 1, content: "examined" },
      { id: 2, content: "examination" },
      { id: 3, content: "exam" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "examined",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "Your test came back___.You are healthy!",
    answers: [
      { id: 1, content: "positive" },
      { id: 2, content: "increase" },
      { id: 3, content: "negative" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "negative",
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question:
      "If someone is  HIV- ___ , it means that he/she has the HIV virus.",
    answers: [
      { id: 1, content: "neutral" },
      { id: 2, content: "positive" },
      { id: 3, content: "negative" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "positive",
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question:
      "If you give someone a 'clean___'  it means that you have determined that the person is completely healthy.",
    answers: [
      { id: 1, content: "bill of health" },
      { id: 2, content: "sheet of health" },
      { id: 3, content: "paper of health" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "bill of health",
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: "What's another word for 'doctor'",
    answers: [
      { id: 1, content: "shrink" },
      { id: 2, content: "physician" },
      { id: 3, content: "physiologist" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "physician",
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: "My mother has a ___ of needles.=She is afraid of needles.'",
    answers: [
      { id: 1, content: "horror" },
      { id: 2, content: "fear" },
      { id: 3, content: "panic" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "fear",
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: "Hopefully we can ___(=find out) what's wrong with you.'",
    answers: [
      { id: 1, content: "name" },
      { id: 2, content: "deter" },
      { id: 3, content: "determine" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "determine",
  },
];
